TAP version 13
# Subtest: all twenty exact Wix brackets and every requested boundary; Canada has a valid finite maximum
ok 1 - all twenty exact Wix brackets and every requested boundary; Canada has a valid finite maximum
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.0167
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: specific disabled zones never fall through; exclusions win; invalid bands and overlapping assignments reject
ok 2 - specific disabled zones never fall through; exclusions win; invalid bands and overlapping assignments reject
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7421
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: exact units and free shipping use merchandise subtotal only within coverage
ok 3 - exact units and free shipping use merchandise subtotal only within coverage
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3479
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: D1 draft publication, weights, independent provider cost, stale quote rejection and zero provider effects on invalid carts
ok 4 - D1 draft publication, weights, independent provider cost, stale quote rejection and zero provider effects on invalid carts
  ---
  duration_ms: 4333.006
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..4
# tests 4
# suites 0
# pass 4
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 4784.0525
