TAP version 13
# Subtest: PayPal money conversion is exact integer CAD arithmetic
ok 1 - PayPal money conversion is exact integer CAD arithmetic
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.9052
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal client keeps Sandbox and Live OAuth and Orders endpoints separate
ok 2 - PayPal client keeps Sandbox and Live OAuth and Orders endpoints separate
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.1954
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: emergency store pause preserves the independently enabled donation path
ok 3 - emergency store pause preserves the independently enabled donation path
  ---
  duration_ms: 4381.5493
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: LIVE donation capture authority projects Live configuration while store creation remains structurally closed
ok 4 - LIVE donation capture authority projects Live configuration while store creation remains structurally closed
  ---
  duration_ms: 5149.7944
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: one-time donation is local-first, idempotent, server-created, and server-captured
ok 5 - one-time donation is local-first, idempotent, server-created, and server-captured
  ---
  duration_ms: 4123.7058
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: an authenticated Master donation lazily creates the canonical customer and account message
ok 6 - an authenticated Master donation lazily creates the canonical customer and account message
  ---
  duration_ms: 4558.8715
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: store order persists authoritative customer, delivery, totals, and PayPal attempt before provider approval
ok 7 - store order persists authoritative customer, delivery, totals, and PayPal attempt before provider approval
  ---
  duration_ms: 4278.2714
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: an environment Master purchase uses its canonical customer and receives only its transactional account message
ok 8 - an environment Master purchase uses its canonical customer and receives only its transactional account message
  ---
  duration_ms: 4656.8128
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal webhook verifies the exact raw event and unresolved delivery enters bounded recovery
ok 9 - PayPal webhook verifies the exact raw event and unresolved delivery enters bounded recovery
  ---
  duration_ms: 3996.7153
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal webhook rejects non-PayPal certificate hosts before provider access
ok 10 - PayPal webhook rejects non-PayPal certificate hosts before provider access
  ---
  duration_ms: 4066.1358
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: verified refund after completion updates donation authority once without fulfillment
ok 11 - verified refund after completion updates donation authority once without fulfillment
  ---
  duration_ms: 3835.9536
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: delivery normalization is bounded, canonical, country-aware, and does not claim verification
ok 12 - delivery normalization is bounded, canonical, country-aware, and does not claim verification
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.5013
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: shipping quote fails before provider fetch while strategy is unconfigured
ok 13 - shipping quote fails before provider fetch while strategy is unconfigured
  ---
  duration_ms: 4128.3412
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: stable Printful v1 shipping adapter uses Catalog variant IDs and normalizes integer CAD
ok 14 - stable Printful v1 shipping adapter uses Catalog variant IDs and normalizes integer CAD
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.4125
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: quote binds authoritative cart and recipient, then checkout snapshots encrypted delivery and Stripe-ready total
ok 15 - quote binds authoritative cart and recipient, then checkout snapshots encrypted delivery and Stripe-ready total
  ---
  duration_ms: 4251.1505
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout rejects changed cart, recipient, expired quote, selected option, forged fields, and environment mismatch
ok 16 - checkout rejects changed cart, recipient, expired quote, selected option, forged fields, and environment mismatch
  ---
  duration_ms: 16997.1291
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: worldwide destinations use authoritative quotes with no Canada-only or universal-postcode restriction
ok 17 - worldwide destinations use authoritative quotes with no Canada-only or universal-postcode restriction
  ---
  duration_ms: 4666.8504
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: international no-postcode recipients survive draft validation and production payload construction
ok 18 - international no-postcode recipients survive draft validation and production payload construction
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.4192
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
ok 19 - safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
  ---
  duration_ms: 4963.7634
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
ok 20 - canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
  ---
  duration_ms: 5694.6395
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
ok 21 - activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
  ---
  duration_ms: 5192.1584
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
ok 22 - failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
  ---
  duration_ms: 5243.1517
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
ok 23 - a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
  ---
  duration_ms: 5037.34
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
ok 24 - save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 5351.068
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
ok 25 - scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
  ---
  duration_ms: 5714.0917
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
ok 26 - general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
  ---
  duration_ms: 4770.4793
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: permanent activation route requires a real local Master session, CSRF and exact production origin
ok 27 - permanent activation route requires a real local Master session, CSRF and exact production origin
  ---
  duration_ms: 4852.7878
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: unchanged operations heartbeat does not stale an otherwise current launch review
ok 28 - unchanged operations heartbeat does not stale an otherwise current launch review
  ---
  duration_ms: 4459.8831
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..28
# tests 28
# suites 0
# pass 28
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 121950.062
