TAP version 13
# Subtest: business control plane masks sensitive identity and derives grouped readiness from canonical authority
ok 1 - business control plane masks sensitive identity and derives grouped readiness from canonical authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 3347.9334
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: commerce.view can read business state while mutations require commerce.business.manage
ok 2 - commerce.view can read business state while mutations require commerce.business.manage
  ---
  duration_ms: 3312.4494
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: business mutation rejects malformed fields and stale revisions while accepting unconventional address text
ok 3 - business mutation rejects malformed fields and stale revisions while accepting unconventional address text
  ---
  duration_ms: 3348.3295
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: business audit records changed categories without plaintext and profile save performs no provider work
ok 4 - business audit records changed categories without plaintext and profile save performs no provider work
  ---
  duration_ms: 3631.8051
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
ok 5 - safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
  ---
  duration_ms: 4455.569
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
ok 6 - canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
  ---
  duration_ms: 4683.7274
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
ok 7 - activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
  ---
  duration_ms: 4055.8563
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
ok 8 - failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
  ---
  duration_ms: 3926.7576
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
ok 9 - a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
  ---
  duration_ms: 4123.2736
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
ok 10 - save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 4563.2975
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
ok 11 - scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
  ---
  duration_ms: 4576.7169
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
ok 12 - general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
  ---
  duration_ms: 3840.3249
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: permanent activation route requires a real local Master session, CSRF and exact production origin
ok 13 - permanent activation route requires a real local Master session, CSRF and exact production origin
  ---
  duration_ms: 3871.341
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: unchanged operations heartbeat does not stale an otherwise current launch review
ok 14 - unchanged operations heartbeat does not stale an otherwise current launch review
  ---
  duration_ms: 4241.9571
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..14
# tests 14
# suites 0
# pass 14
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 56908.734
