TAP version 13
# Subtest: save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
ok 1 - save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 5317.6926
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: permanent activation route requires a real local Master session, CSRF and exact production origin
ok 2 - permanent activation route requires a real local Master session, CSRF and exact production origin
  ---
  duration_ms: 5371.3347
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..2
# tests 2
# suites 0
# pass 2
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 11224.4994
