TAP version 13
# Subtest: PayPal money conversion is exact integer CAD arithmetic
ok 1 - PayPal money conversion is exact integer CAD arithmetic
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.9888
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal client keeps Sandbox and Live OAuth and Orders endpoints separate
ok 2 - PayPal client keeps Sandbox and Live OAuth and Orders endpoints separate
  ---
  duration_ms: 6.0329
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: emergency store pause preserves the independently enabled donation path
ok 3 - emergency store pause preserves the independently enabled donation path
  ---
  duration_ms: 3573.616
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: LIVE donation capture authority projects Live configuration while store creation remains structurally closed
ok 4 - LIVE donation capture authority projects Live configuration while store creation remains structurally closed
  ---
  duration_ms: 3339.153
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: one-time donation is local-first, idempotent, server-created, and server-captured
ok 5 - one-time donation is local-first, idempotent, server-created, and server-captured
  ---
  duration_ms: 3567.0706
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: an authenticated Master donation lazily creates the canonical customer and account message
ok 6 - an authenticated Master donation lazily creates the canonical customer and account message
  ---
  duration_ms: 3393.476
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: store order persists authoritative customer, delivery, totals, and PayPal attempt before provider approval
ok 7 - store order persists authoritative customer, delivery, totals, and PayPal attempt before provider approval
  ---
  duration_ms: 3561.2481
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: an environment Master purchase uses its canonical customer and receives only its transactional account message
ok 8 - an environment Master purchase uses its canonical customer and receives only its transactional account message
  ---
  duration_ms: 3519.4373
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal webhook verifies the exact raw event and unresolved delivery enters bounded recovery
ok 9 - PayPal webhook verifies the exact raw event and unresolved delivery enters bounded recovery
  ---
  duration_ms: 3493.2029
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal webhook rejects non-PayPal certificate hosts before provider access
ok 10 - PayPal webhook rejects non-PayPal certificate hosts before provider access
  ---
  duration_ms: 3344.521
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: verified refund after completion updates donation authority once without fulfillment
ok 11 - verified refund after completion updates donation authority once without fulfillment
  ---
  duration_ms: 3303.9582
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
ok 12 - safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
  ---
  duration_ms: 3739.1031
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
ok 13 - canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
  ---
  duration_ms: 4223.0387
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
ok 14 - activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
  ---
  duration_ms: 3792.2964
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
ok 15 - failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
  ---
  duration_ms: 3640.9377
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
ok 16 - a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
  ---
  duration_ms: 3943.0954
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
ok 17 - save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 3936.1021
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
ok 18 - scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
  ---
  duration_ms: 4446.1664
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
ok 19 - general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
  ---
  duration_ms: 3594.7064
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..19
# tests 19
# suites 0
# pass 19
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 63372.1701
