TAP version 13
# Subtest: safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
ok 1 - safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
  ---
  duration_ms: 3977.9071
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
ok 2 - canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
  ---
  duration_ms: 4686.109
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
ok 3 - activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
  ---
  duration_ms: 4236.0169
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
ok 4 - failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
  ---
  duration_ms: 4013.3149
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
ok 5 - a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
  ---
  duration_ms: 4097.4095
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
ok 6 - save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 4189.724
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
ok 7 - scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
  ---
  duration_ms: 4599.7023
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
ok 8 - general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
  ---
  duration_ms: 3988.1177
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: permanent activation route requires a real local Master session, CSRF and exact production origin
ok 9 - permanent activation route requires a real local Master session, CSRF and exact production origin
  ---
  duration_ms: 4341.4022
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: unchanged operations heartbeat does not stale an otherwise current launch review
ok 10 - unchanged operations heartbeat does not stale an otherwise current launch review
  ---
  duration_ms: 4777.1228
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Master launch control at 1440, 768 and 390 supports masked review, explicit confirmation, atomic edits, LIVE and emergency pause
ok 11 - Master launch control at 1440, 768 and 390 supports masked review, explicit confirmation, atomic edits, LIVE and emergency pause
  ---
  duration_ms: 8265.5632
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..11
# tests 11
# suites 0
# pass 11
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 52251.6469
