TAP version 13
# Subtest: PayPal money conversion is exact integer CAD arithmetic
ok 1 - PayPal money conversion is exact integer CAD arithmetic
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0086
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal client keeps Sandbox and Live OAuth and Orders endpoints separate
ok 2 - PayPal client keeps Sandbox and Live OAuth and Orders endpoints separate
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.5007
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: emergency store pause preserves the independently enabled donation path
ok 3 - emergency store pause preserves the independently enabled donation path
  ---
  duration_ms: 3413.8738
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: LIVE donation capture authority projects Live configuration while store creation remains structurally closed
ok 4 - LIVE donation capture authority projects Live configuration while store creation remains structurally closed
  ---
  duration_ms: 3185.2671
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: one-time donation is local-first, idempotent, server-created, and server-captured
ok 5 - one-time donation is local-first, idempotent, server-created, and server-captured
  ---
  duration_ms: 3419.9843
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: an authenticated Master donation lazily creates the canonical customer and account message
ok 6 - an authenticated Master donation lazily creates the canonical customer and account message
  ---
  duration_ms: 3264.6506
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: store order persists authoritative customer, delivery, totals, and PayPal attempt before provider approval
ok 7 - store order persists authoritative customer, delivery, totals, and PayPal attempt before provider approval
  ---
  duration_ms: 3417.7111
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: an environment Master purchase uses its canonical customer and receives only its transactional account message
ok 8 - an environment Master purchase uses its canonical customer and receives only its transactional account message
  ---
  duration_ms: 3384.6702
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal webhook verifies the exact raw event and unresolved delivery enters bounded recovery
ok 9 - PayPal webhook verifies the exact raw event and unresolved delivery enters bounded recovery
  ---
  duration_ms: 3191.9104
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PayPal webhook rejects non-PayPal certificate hosts before provider access
ok 10 - PayPal webhook rejects non-PayPal certificate hosts before provider access
  ---
  duration_ms: 3205.4608
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: verified refund after completion updates donation authority once without fulfillment
ok 11 - verified refund after completion updates donation authority once without fulfillment
  ---
  duration_ms: 3258.0267
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
ok 12 - safe unconventional private values persist, decrypt, reload and reject malformed replacements
  ---
  duration_ms: 3623.1939
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
ok 13 - canonical readiness excludes Stripe, invoices, shipment and signed-webhook evidence; activation is coherent and idempotent
  ---
  duration_ms: 3984.1311
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
ok 14 - activation requires both attestations and current readiness and profile revisions
  ---
  duration_ms: 3759.1554
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
ok 15 - failed activation write rolls back settings, owner attestation, profile edits and audit
  ---
  duration_ms: 3810.0545
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
ok 16 - a concurrent gate change inside activation is caught before any activation writes
  ---
  duration_ms: 3574.6071
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
ok 17 - save and activate accepts the latest edits in one transaction and subsequent saves invalidate revision-bound authority
  ---
  duration_ms: 3768.4968
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
ok 18 - scoped review and acceptance precede PayPal; retained agreement and encrypted receipt are immutable
  ---
  duration_ms: 4135.0598
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
ok 19 - general browser projections and PayPal configuration never expose encrypted private records
  ---
  duration_ms: 3457.695
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..19
# tests 19
# suites 0
# pass 19
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 60823.4704
