TAP version 13
# Subtest: quote binds authoritative cart and recipient, then checkout snapshots encrypted delivery and Stripe-ready total
ok 1 - quote binds authoritative cart and recipient, then checkout snapshots encrypted delivery and Stripe-ready total
  ---
  duration_ms: 3778.6213
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..1
# tests 1
# suites 0
# pass 1
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 4205.6489
